A Guide to the Foundation for Child Development records FA019
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administration, 1950-1996; bulk; 1
  - Administration - Committees, 1950-1992, 1996; bulk; 2
    - Executive Committee, February 15, 1965 (Reel 20, Frame 306)
    - Executive Committee, June 21, 1965 (Reel 20, Frame 369)
    - Executive Committee, September 27, 1965 (Reel 20, Frame 411)
    - Executive Committee, November 22, 1965 (Reel 20, Frame 479)
    - Executive Committee, December 13, 1965 (Reel 20, Frame 510)
    - Executive Committee, February 21, 1966 (Reel 20, Frame 533)
    - Executive Committee, March 31, 1966 (Reel 20, Frame 562)
    - Executive Committee, April 18, 1966 (Reel 20, Frame 600)
    - Executive Committee, October 17, 1966 (Reel 20, Frame 603)
    - Executive Committee, December 12, 1966 (Reel 20, Frame 632)
    - Executive Committee, February 20, 1967 (Reel 20, Frame 653)
    - Executive Committee, May 8, 1967 (Reel 20, Frame 705)
    - Executive Committee, June 12, 1967 (Reel 20, Frame 738)
    - Executive Committee, December 12, 1967 (Reel 20, Frame 757)
    - Executive Committee, March 19, 1968 (Reel 20, Frame 789)
    - Executive Committee, June 24, 1968 (Reel 20, Frame 801)
    - Executive Committee, July 29, 1968 (Reel 20, Frame 840)
    - Executive Committee, September 23, 1968 (Reel 20, Frame 869)
    - Executive Committee, November 18, 1968 (Reel 20, Frame 923)
    - Executive Committee, February 17, 1969 (Reel 20, Frame 958)
    - Executive Committee, March 17, 1969 (Reel 20, Frame 1022)
    - Executive Committee, December 15, 1969 (Reel 20, Frame 1028)
    - Executive Committee, June 15, 1990 (Reel 20, Frame 1068)
    - Executive Committee, October 22, 1970 (Reel 20, Frame 1128)
    - Executive Committee, June 24, 1971 (Reel 21, Frame 4)
      Grants 492, 493
    - Executive Committee, November 18, 1971 (Reel 21, Frame 79)
      Grant 497
    - Executive Committee, April 27, 1972 (Reel 21, Frame 114)
    - Executive Committee, November 8, 1972 (Reel 21, Frame 146)
    - Executive Committee, April 26, 1973 (Reel 21, Frame 181)
    - Executive Committee, April 18, 1974 (Reel 21, Frame 193)
    - Executive Committee, July 16, 1974 (Reel 21, Frame 216)
    - Executive Committee, May 4, 1976 (Reel 21, Frame 252)
    - Executive Committee, April 17, 1979 (Reel 21, Frame 272)
    - Executive Committee, April 14, 1983 (Reel 21, Frame 307)
    - Executive Committee, May 4, 1987 (Reel 21, Frame 341)
    - Executive Committee, January 30, 1989 (Reel 21, Frame 408)
    - Executive Committee, May 30, 1990 (Reel 21, Frame 424)
    - Executive Committee, January 29, 1991 (Reel 21, Frame 466)
    - Executive Committee, February 22, 1991 (Reel 21, Frame 493)
    - Executive Committee, April 24, 1991 (Reel 21, Frame 497)
    - Executive Committee, September 26, 1991 (Reel 21, Frame 507)
    - Executive Committee, February 11, 1992 (Reel 21, Frame 517)
    - Executive Committee, May 19, 1992 (Reel 21, Frame 524)
    - Executive Committee, November 12, 1992 (Reel 21, Frame 542)
    - Executive Committee, January 16, 1996 (Reel 21, Frame 564)
    - Executive Committee, November 6, 1996 (Reel 21, Frame 593)
    - Nominating Committee, 1955-1967 (Reel 21, Frame 621)
    - Nominating Committee, 1968-1971 (Reel 21, Frame 780)
    - Nominating Committee, 1972-1976 (Reel 21, Frame 883)
    - Nominating Committee, 1977-1980 (Reel 21, Frame 981)
    - Nominating Committee, 1981-1983 (Reel 22, Frame 4)
    - Nominating Committee, 1984-1986 (Reel 22, Frame 156)
    - Nominating Committee, 1987-1989 (Reel 22, Frame 325)
    - Nominating Committee, 1990-1991 (Reel 22, Frame 521)
    - Nominating Committee, 1992 (Reel 22, Frame 639)
    - Nominating Committee - Candidate Resumes, 1992 (Reel 22, Frame 837)
    - Nominating Committee, 1996 (Reel 23, Frame 4)
    - Personnel Committee, May 15, 1963 (Reel 23, Frame 84)
    - Personnel Committee, December 11, 1963 (Reel 23, Frame 93)
    - Personnel Committee, February 17, 1965 (Reel 23, Frame 96)
    - Personnel Committee, February 1, 1968 (Reel 23, Frame 112)
    - Personnel Committee, February 4, 1969 (Reel 23, Frame 130)
    - Program Advisory Committee, 1980 (Reel 23, Frame 151)
    - Program Advisory Group, 1971-1973 (Reel 23, Frame 154)
      Formerly 'Meetings of Staff'
    - Scientific Review Committee on Human Fetal Development, 1967 (Reel 23, Frame 243)
  - Administration - Council, 1951-1996; 3
    This subseries is arranged in two sub-subseries:
    Sub-subseries 1 - Meetings of the Council
    Sub-subseries 2 - Members of the Council
    - Meetings of the Council, 1951-1992, 1996; 1
      This subseries contains minutes of Council meetings for the period 1951-1992 and 1996.
      - Meetings of the Council, 1951-1992, 1996 (Reel 23, Frame 251)
      - May 9, 1951 (Reel 23, Frame 252)
      - April 23, 1952 (Reel 23, Frame 295)
      - April 29, 1953 (Reel 23, Frame 317)
      - May 3, 1954 (Reel 23, Frame 324)
      - April 25, 1955 (Reel 23, Frame 333)
      - April 30, 1956 (Reel 23, Frame 347)
      - October 24, 1956 (Reel 23, Frame 359)
      - April 30, 1957 (Reel 23, Frame 369)
      - November 13, 1957 (Reel 23, Frame 383)
      - May 5, 1958 (Reel 23, Frame 389)
      - January 21, 1959 (Reel 23, Frame 399)
      - April 29, 1959 (Reel 23, Frame 406)
      - November 10, 1959 (Reel 23, Frame 414)
      - February 4, 1960 (Reel 23, Frame 423)
      - April 13, 1960 (Reel 23, Frame 441)
      - November 16, 1960 (Reel 23, Frame 456)
      - February 8, 1961 (Reel 23, Frame 476)
      - April 26, 1961 (Reel 23, Frame 484)
      - November 9, 1961 (Reel 23, Frame 502)
      - February 8, 1962 (Reel 23, Frame 510)
      - April 18, 1962 (Reel 23, Frame 538)
      - November 19, 1962 (Reel 23, Frame 560)
      - April 23, 1963 (Reel 23, Frame 594)
      - April 20, 1964 (Reel 23, Frame 655)
      - November 30, 1964 (Reel 23, Frame 673)
      - April 19, 1965 (Reel 23, Frame 711)
      - November 22, 1965 (Reel 23, Frame 718)
      - April 18, 1966 (Reel 23, Frame 722)
      - November 21, 1966 (Reel 23, Frame 734)
      - April 17, 1967 (Reel 23, Frame 738)
      - April 16, 1968 (Reel 23, Frame 783)
      - April 21, 1969 (Reel 23, Frame 791)
      - April 13, 1970 (Reel 23, Frame 802)
      - April 22, 1971 (Reel 23, Frame 815)
      - September 28, 1972 (Reel 23, Frame 838)
      - September 25, 1973 (Reel 23, Frame 875)
      - September 18, 1974 (Reel 23, Frame 901)
      - September 17, 1975 (Reel 23, Frame 934)
      - September 15, 1976 (Reel 23, Frame 970)
      - September 14, 1977 (Reel 23, Frame 994)
      - September 20, 1978 (Reel 23, Frame 1029)
      - September 19, 1979 (Reel 23, Frame 1055)
      - September 25, 1980 (Reel 23, Frame 1074)
      - September 24, 1981 (Reel 23, Frame 1104)
      - September 23, 1982 (Reel 23, Frame 1130)
      - September 22, 1983 (Reel 24, Frame 3)
      - September 20, 1984 (Reel 24, Frame 35)
      - September 26, 1985 (Reel 24, Frame 58)
      - September 25, 1986 (Reel 24, Frame 73)
      - September 17, 1987 (Reel 24, Frame 99)
      - September 15, 1988 (Reel 24, Frame 101)
      - September 21, 1989 (Reel 24, Frame 127)
      - September 27, 1990 (Reel 24, Frame 132)
      - September 26, 1991 (Reel 24, Frame 177)
      - September 24, 1992 (Reel 24, Frame 229)
      - September 19, 1996 (Reel 24, Frame 341)
    - Members of the Council, 1951-1995; 2
      Separated Materials
      Audio cassettes of interviews dated April 1994 with Emily McFarland, Kathleen Mortimer, and George M. Wheatley are found in Series 6, Audio-visual materials.
      This subseries contains biographical information regarding Council members and their terms of involvement in the organization.
      Oral history interviews were conducted with eleven members of the council, who served terms between 1951 and 1955. These interviews provide a perspective on the post-World War II Foundation and the development of the organization after the acceptance of the Belding funds. This historical information was intended to supplement the Foundation's narrative history written by Alice FitzGerald. This subseries includes the transcripts of interviews conducted with the following individuals: Dr. Herbert G. Birch and Stephen A. Richardson; Lewis B. Cuyler; Charles Dollard; Jessie K. Emmet; Alice FitzGerald; Emily F. McFarland; Leonard Mayo; and Milton J. E. Senn.
      Transcripts do not exist for the oral history interviews of Kathleen Mortimer and George M. Wheatley.
      - Series 1.3.2 - Administration - Council - Members of the Council, 1951-1995 (Reel 24, Frame 412)
      - Henry L. Barnett, 1966-1970, 1972, 1975, 1978, 1981-1982, 1984, 1987-1988, 1992-1993 (Reel 24, Frame 414)
      - Leona Baumgartner, 1954-1963, 1965, 1967-1970, 1972, 1974, 1979, 1982, 1985 (Reel 24, Frame 704)
      - Andrew Billingsley, 1977-1986, 1988-1989, 1992, 1998 (Reel 24, Frame 807)
      - Herbert G. Birch and Stephen A. Richardson - Oral History Interview Transcript, 1972 (Reel 24, Frame 880)
      - Mary Braga, 1971-1972 (Reel 24, Frame 895)
      - Katharine E. Bull, 1954, 1957, 1959, 1960, 1962, 1965, 1972, 1974, 1980, 1984 (Reel 24, Frame 992)
      - Hillary Rodham Clinton, 1988-1989, 1991 (Reel 24, Frame 1035)
      - John Adam Clausen, 1959-1962, 1965, 1972, 1974-1977, 1979 (Reel 24, Frame 1047)
      - John Crichton, 1977-1978 (Reel 24, Frame 1111)
      - Jean A. Curran, 1951, 1953-1957, 1959-1964, 1966-1967, 1969-1975, 1977 (Reel 25, Frame 3)
      - Lewis B. Cuyler, 1953, 1955-1967, 1969-1972, 1974, 1979-1980, 1982, 1985, 1988 (Reel 25, Frame 273)
      - Lewis B. Cuyler - Oral History Interview Transcript, 1972 (Reel 25, Frame 577)
      - Arthur H. Dean, 1953-1968, 1974 (Reel 25, Frame 641)
      - Jane L. Delgado, 1989-1998 (Reel 25, Frame 678)
      - J. Richardson Dilworth, 1955, 1957-1964, 1967, 1976 (Reel 25, Frame 856)
      - Charles Dollard, 1955-1972, 1975-1977 (Reel 25, Frame 896)
      - Charles Dollard - Oral History Interview Transcript, 1972 (Reel 25, Frame 1115)
      - Peter W. Eccles, 1970, 1973, 1975, 1976, 1980, 1983, 1992-1993 (Reel 25, Frame 1151)
      - Peter B. Edelman, 1993 (Reel 25, Frame 1187)
      - Jessie K. Emmet, 1953-1960, 1962-1965, 1968-1972, 1974-1975, 1977, 1980-1982 (Reel 26, Frame 3)
      - Jessie K. Emmet - Oral History Interview Transcript, 1972 (Reel 26, Frame 153)
      - Alice FitzGerald, 1957, 1961, 1963-1965, 1967-1972, 1975-1976, 1979-1980, 1982, 1985-1986 (Reel 26, Frame 202)
      - Alice FitzGerald - Oral History Interview Transcript, 1972 (Reel 26, Frame 277)
      - Nevil Ford, 1952-1972, 1974, 1978-1979 (Reel 26, Frame 362)
      - Fritz Fuchs, 1970-1972, 1975-1976, 1981, 1983-1984, 1988, 1990 (Reel 26, Frame 636)
      - Howard L. Fuller, 1988, 1991, 1993-1995 (Reel 26, Frame 689)
      - George J. W. Goodman, 1985-1988 (Reel 26, Frame 744)
        Information about Adam Smith, a Council member from 1984-1988, can be found in this folder.
      - Martie Hermann, 1952-1954, 1956, 1958-1966, 1974, 1980 (Reel 26, Frame 808)
      - Kennett W. Hinks, 1954-1955, 1958-1963, 1965, 1969-1970, 1975, 1981-1982 (Reel 26, Frame 860)
      - Robert F. Hoerle, 1995, 1998 (Reel 26, Frame 919)
      - John W. Holman, Jr., 1970-1977, 1980-1988 (Reel 26, Frame 925)
      - Charlayne Hunter-Gault, 1983-1986 (Reel 26, Frame 1000)
      - Eleanor Keil, 1962, 1965, 1972, 1974, 1980, 1983 (Reel 26, Frame 1022)
      - Seymour Kety, 1964, 1968-1969, 1971, 1982 (Reel 26, Frame 1047)
      - Sara L. Lightfoot, 1977-1990 (Reel 26, Frame 1097)
      - Lee J. Marino, 1953-1972 (Reel 27, Frame 3)
      - Leonard W. Mayo, 1953-1955, 1960-1962, 1965-1973, 1975-1976, 1979-1990, 1992 (Reel 27, Frame 53)
      - Leonard W. Mayo - Oral History Transcript, 1972 (Reel 27, Frame 431)
      - Ross A. McFarland, 1953-1955, 1957-1962, 1964, 1967-1969, 1972-1973, 1975-1976 (Reel 27, Frame 511)
      - McFarland, Emily - Oral History Transcript, 1972 (Reel 27, Frame 707)
      - Janet C. Morgan, 1953, 1955, 1957-1967, 1976, 1979, 1982, 1985-1986 (Reel 27, Frame 742)
      - Robert S. Morison, 1954-1970, 1975-1977, 1980 (Reel 27, Frame 811)
      - William H. Morton, 1968, 1974 (Reel 27, Frame 899)
      - Johanna Mosenthal, 1953-1954, 1957, 1960, 1963, 1966 (Reel 27, Frame 905)
      - Katherine Neuberger, 1953-1961, 1963-1964, 1966-1967, 1969-1970, 1975 (Reel 27, Frame 928)
      - I. Gertrude Ogden, 1953, 1959, 1962, 1965-1966, 1972, 1974, 1980, 1983, 1986 (Reel 27, Frame 971)
      - Emil Pattberg, Jr., 1956-1972, 1974 (Reel 27, Frame 992)
      - Harvey Picker, 1976-1977, 1979-1982, 1984 (Reel 27, Frame 1082)
      - Stanley R. Resor, 1956-1966, 1973 (Reel 28, Frame 3)
      - Nancy Riker, 1952-1963, 1966-1967, 1970-1971, 1975-1978 (Reel 28, Frame 130)
      - Mary F. Rockefeller, 1952, 1954-1955, 1957-1960, 1962, 1965, 1971-1972, 1974, 1980, 1983, 1994, 1997 (Reel 28, Frame 192)
      - George Rosen, 1963-1964, 1966, 1969, 1975 (Reel 28, Frame 224)
      - Cynthia Saltzman, 1954, 1956-1965, 1967, 1979, 1982, 1985, 1988 (Reel 28, Frame 296)
      - Milton J. E. Senn, 1955-1956, 1958-1964, 1966-1977, 1979, 1982-1983 (Reel 28, Frame 363)
      - Milton J. E. Senn - Oral History Project, 1972, 1974-1975 (Reel 28, Frame 520)
        - Interview with Orville Brim, February 12, 1973 (Reel 28, Frame 534)
        - Interview with Orville Brim, February 26, 1975 (Reel 28, Frame 547)
        - Interview with Urie Bronfenbrenner, April 12, 1972 (Reel 28, Frame 562)
        - Interview with George J. Hecht, July 27, 1972 (Reel 28, Frame 600)
        - Interview with Senator Walter Mondale, April 23, 1975 (Reel 28, Frame 620)
        - Interview with Congressman Albert Quie, April 25, 1975 (Reel 28, Frame 635)
        - Interview with Benjamin Spock, November 20, 1974 (Reel 28, Frame 659)
        - Interview with Edward Zigler, June 10, 1972 (Reel 28, Frame 702)
      - Milton J. E. Senn - Oral History Transcript, 1972 (Reel 28, Frame 735)
      - Alfred R. Shands, 1955, 1958-1961, 1963-1964, 1966-1967, 1969-1970, 1972-1973 (Reel 28, Frame 785)
      - Theodore Sizer, 1980-1984, 1990, 1992, 1997 (Reel 28, Frame 825)
      - J. Kellum Smith, 1968, 1972, 1973-1975, 1980-1983, 1986, 1990 (Reel 28, Frame 889)
      - Phoebe Stein, 1970, 1976, 1979 (Reel 28, Frame 921)
      - Gilbert Steiner, 1980-1984, 1987-1994, 1996 (Reel 28, Frame 927)
      - George S. Stevenson, 1954-1959, 1961-1964, 1967, 1970, 1976, 1979, 1982, 1983 (Reel 28, Frame 985)
      - Candace Straight, 1983-1985 (Reel 28, Frame 1052)
      - Mary E. Switzer, 1956-1958, 1960-1967, 1969-1972 (Reel 28, Frame 1070)
      - Campbell T. Thompson, 1954-1955, 1961, 1964, 1967, 1974 (Reel 29, Frame 3)
      - Walter L. Wallace, 1974-1976, 1980-1985, 1992 (Reel 29, Frame 17)
      - Kerr L. White, 1967-1977, 1979, 1981, 1984 (Reel 29, Frame 76)
      - Henry S. Wingate, 1952-1960, 1963, 1965-1967, 1969-1972, 1974-1975, 1980-1983 (Reel 29, Frame 231)
  - Administration - President's Files, Barbara Blum, 1975-1996; 4
    Biographical / Historical
    President Barbara Blum directed the Foundation from 1986-1996. Prior to her tenure at FCD, she was involved in the planning of the Child Welfare Reform Act of 1979 and was Commissioner of Social Services of the State of New York during Governor Hugh Carey's term.
    Numerous presentations on behalf of the Foundation are included in this material.
    General note
    Actual dates for this Subseries are 1975, 1977-1982, 1989-1994, 1996.
    - President's Files, Barbara Blum, 1975, 1977-1982, 1989-1994, 1996 (Reel 29, Frame 307)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1975, 1977-1982 (Reel 29, Frame 308)
    - Board Correspondence, 1992, 1996 (Reel 29, Frame 617)
    - Child Welfare Reform Act of 1979: Planning and Implementation Activities (Draft), 1982 (Reel 29, Frame 702)
    - Commissioner of Social Services, State of New York, 1977-1978, 1982 (Reel 29, Frame 902)
    - Commissioner of Social Services, State of New York - Personal Correspondence, 1977-1982 (Reel 30, Frame 1)
    - Manpower Demonstration Research Corporation, 1981-1982 (Reel 30, Frame 200)
    - National Council of State Public Welfare Administrators, 1979-1980 (Reel 30, Frame 428)
    - National Council of State Public Welfare Administrators, 1981 (Reel 30, Frame 714)
    - National Council of State Public Welfare Administrators, 1982 (Reel 31, Frame 1)
    - National Research Council, 1981 (Reel 31, Frame 176)
    - Permanent Interagency Committee on Early Childhood Programs, 1989-1990 (Reel 31, Frame 193)
    - Permanent Interagency Committee on Early Childhood Programs, 1991 (Reel 31, Frame 312)
    - Permanent Interagency Committee on Early Childhood Programs, 1992-1994 (Reel 31, Frame 785)
    - Testimony and Speeches, 1980 (Reel 31, Frame 917)
    - Testimony and Speeches, 1981 (Reel 32, Frame 1)
    - Testimony and Speeches, 1982 (Reel 32, Frame 266)
    - Testimony and Speeches, 1986 (Reel 32, Frame 454)
- Annual Reports, 1898-1998; 2
  The archival material has been reformatted. Access to the original archival material is restricted. User copies of the microfilm are available for scholarly access.
  Existence and Location of Copies
  Copies of the Annual Reports for later years are also available in the Archive Center's reference library.
  The Annual Reports of the FCD span one full century, from the inception of the organization known as the Guild for the Crippled Children of the Poor of New York City in 1898 through the late twentieth century. This series contains Annual Reports for the years 1898, 1902, 1904, 1907, 1909-1910, 1912-1934, 1946-1998. There is also a comprehensive report for the period 1900-1945.
  - Second Annual Report of the Guild for the Crippled Children of the Poor of New York City, May 1898 (Reel 32, Frame 550, Box 1, Folder 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Access to the original archival material is restricted. User copies of the microfilm are available for scholarly access.
  - Fourth Annual Report of the Guild for the Crippled Children of the Poor of New York City, January 1902 (Box 1, Folder 2, Reel 32, Frame 560)
  - Report of Work Among the Crippled Children of the Tenements of New York City, 1904 (Reel 32, Frame 572, Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Sixth Report of the Guild for Crippled Children of the Poor of New York City, 1907 (Reel 32, Frame 583, Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1909 (Reel 32, Frame 596, Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1910 (Reel 32, Frame 609, Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 7, Reel 32, Frame 643)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 8, Reel 32, Frame 664)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 9, Reel 32, Frame 677)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Report for the Year Ending October 31, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 10, Reel 32, Frame 687)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Report for the Year Ending October 31, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 11, Reel 32, Frame 701)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Report for the Year Ending October 31, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 12, Reel 32, Frame 723)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1918 and 1919 (Box 1, Folder 13, Reel 32, Frame 745)
  - Opportunities - 20th Annual Report, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 14, Reel 32, Frame 767)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Twenty-Second Annual Report, 1921-1922 (Reel 32, Frame 782, Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Twenty-third Annual Report, October 31, 1921, December 31, 1923 (Reel 32, Frame 802, Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Twenty-Fourth Annual Report of the Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1924-1925 (Reel 32, Frame 822, Box 1, Folder 17)
  - The Twenty-Fifth Annual Report of the Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1925 (Reel 32, Frame 846, Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Annual Report - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1926 (Reel 32, Frame 868, Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Twenty-seventh Annual Report, January 1, 1927-January 1, 1928 (Reel 32, Frame 892, Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Twenty-eighth Annual Report, January 1, 1928-January 1, 1929 (Reel 32, Frame 914, Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Thirtieth Annual Report, 1930 (Reel 32, Frame 950, Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Thirty-first Annual Report, 1931 (Reel 32, Frame 981, Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Thirty-second Annual Report, 1932 (Reel 32, Frame 1011, Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Thirty-third Annual Report, 1933 (Reel 32, Frame 1033, Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Thirty-fourth Annual Report, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 26, Reel 32, Frame 1058)
  - Growth: The Story of Forty-five Years of Service Performed by the Association for the Aid of Crippled Children and its Forerunner, the Class for Crippled Children, 1900-1945, undated (Box 2, Folder 27, Reel 32, Frame 1082)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, A Service for Manhattan, Bronx and Queens - The Past Year, Annual Report for Year Ending March 31, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 28, Reel 32, Frame 1110)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Annual Report for Year Ending March 31, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 29, Reel 32, Frame 1124)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children - Annual Report for Year Ending March 31, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 30, Reel 33, Frame 1)
  - The Story of the 50th Year - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children Annual Report for Year Ending March 31, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 31, Reel 33, Frame 22)
  - Steps to Tomorrow - Annual Report for Year Ending March 31, 1950 (Reel 33, Frame 31, Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Wider Horizons - Annual Report for Year Ending March 31, 1951 (Reel 33, Frame 43, Box 2, Folder 33)
  - "Our Responsibility a Greater Usefulness..." - Annual Report for Year Ending March 31, 1952 (Reel 33, Frame 54, Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Keys to Progress - Annual Report for Year Ending March 31, 1953 (Reel 33, Frame 71, Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Synthesis - Annual Report for Year Ending March 31, 1954 (Reel 33, Frame 87, Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children: Frontiers - Annual Report for the Year Ended March 31, 1955 (Reel 33, Frame 113, Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children: Progress in Prevention - Annual Report for the Year Ended March 31, 1956 (Reel 33, Frame 143, Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children: "For the Record" - Annual Report for the Program Year 1956/1957 (Box 2, Folder 39, Reel 33, Frame 174)
  - New Bearings on Research - Annual Report for the Program Year 1957-1958 (Reel 33, Frame 220, Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Annual Report of the Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1958-1959 (Reel 33, Frame 256, Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Annual Report of the Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 42, Reel 33, Frame 290)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, Annual Report, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 43, Reel 33, Frame 324)
  - Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, Annual Report, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 44, Reel 33, Frame 351)
  - The Association for the Aid of Crippled Children, Biennial Report, 1962-1963/1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 45, Reel 33, Frame 374)
  - Three Year Report, Association for the Aid of Crippled Children for the Fiscal Years 1964-65, 1965-66, 1966-67, undated (Box 2, Folder 46, Reel 33, Frame 409)
  - Three Year Report, Association for the Aid of Crippled Children for the Fiscal Years 1967-1970 (Reel 33, Frame 438, Box 2, Folder 47)